YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 9. Photographs
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. PRINTS AND NEGATIVES
  - Subseries D. International Work
    - Countries
      - Thailand
        - Bazaars, Fashion Shows, 1953-58 (Box 1019, Folder 4)
        - Buildings, 1947-68 (Box 1019, Folder 5)
        - Children and Teens, 1954-71 (Box 1019, Folder 6)
        - Classes, 1950s?, 1968 (Box 1019, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous, 1954-74 (Box 1019, Folder 8)
        - Negatives (Box 1019, Folder 9-10)
      - Trinidad and Tobago, 1967 (Box 1019, Folder 11)
      - Turkey
        - Buildings, 1954-89, n.d. (Box 1019, Folder 12)
        - Camping and Recreation
          - 1920s (Box 1019, Folder 13)
          - 1960-70 (Box 1020, Folder 1)
          - Negatives (Box 1020, Folder 2)
          - 'Cadde Bostan' Summer Camp Scrapbook, 1932 (Box 1020, Folder 3)
        - Children, circa 1950s-73 (Box 1020, Folder 4)
        - Classes
          - Prints, 1926, 1960s (Box 1020, Folder 5)
          - Negatives (Box 1020, Folder 6)
        - Constantinople
          - General, circa 1920-26, 1948, 1961-64 (Box 1020, Folder 7-8)
          - Buildings, 1920-21, n.d. (Box 1020, Folder 9)
        - Miscellaneous, circa 1945-83 (Box 1020, Folder 10)
        - Smyrna (Now Izmir) and Cicilia, 1921-23 (Box 1020, Folder 11)
        - Smyrna Scrapbook, 1922 (Box 1020, Folder 12)
      - Uganda
        - Agricultural Training
          - Prints, 1959-67, n.d. (Box 1020, Folder 13)
          - Negatives (Box 1021, Folder 1)
        - Buildings, Conferences, 1955-63 (Box 1021, Folder 2)
        - Classes and Crafts
          - Prints, 1953-70, n.d. (Box 1021, Folder 3)
          - Negatives (Box 1021, Folder 4)
        - Groups and Meetings
          - Prints, 1953-69, n.d. (Box 1021, Folder 5)
          - Negatives (Box 1021, Folder 6)
        - Health and Nutrition, circa 1953-61 (Box 1021, Folder 7)
        - Program
          - General, 1957-67, n.d. (Box 1021, Folder 8)
          - Snapshots (Box 1021, Folder 9)
        - Women at Work Series
          - Prints, 1950s-60s? (Box 1021, Folder 10)
          - Negatives (Box 1021, Folder 11)
        - Y-Teens, 1950s-65, n.d. (Box 1022, Folder 1)
      - Uruguay
        - Prints, 1921-77, n.d. (Box 1022, Folder 2-3)
        - Negatives (Box 1022, Folder 4)
      - Vietnam, 1968-71 (Box 1022, Folder 5)
      - Yemen, circa 1920s (Box 1022, Folder 6)
      - Zaire, circa 1960s (Box 1022, Folder 7)
      - Zambia (also known as Northern Rhodesia)
        - Prints, 1960-69 (Box 1022, Folder 8)
        - Negatives (Box 1022, Folder 9)
      - Zimbabwe (also known as Rhodesia or Southern Rhodesia)
        - Agriculture - Conferences, 1960-87 (Box 1022, Folder 10)
        - Leadership Training - Y-Teens, 1963-66 (Box 1022, Folder 11)
        - Negatives (Box 1022, Folder 12)
  - Subseries E. Program
    - Advocacy
      - Public Affairs, General, 1961-84, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 1)
      - Demonstrations, Parades, and Protests
        - Prints, 1961-96, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 2-4)
        - Negatives (Box 1023, Folder 5)
      - Institute for Public Leadership, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 6)
    - Personnel and Training
      - General, 1935-85, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 7)
      - American Committee: Secretarial Training Institute, 1898, 1904 (Box 1023, Folder 8)
      - National Training School
        - 3 Gramercy Park, New York City, 1909-11, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 9)
        - 135 West 52nd St., New York City, 1914-20, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 10)
        - Snapshots, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 11)
      - School for Professional Workers, 1951-64, n.d. (Box 1023, Folder 12-14)
      - National YWCA Program Institute for Executive Directors and Program Directors, University of Chicago, 1966 (Box 1023, Folder 15)
      - Public Policy Forum: Empowerment Through Public Policy, May 1990 (Box 1023, Folder 16)
    - Constituent Groups
      - Employed Women, [see also War Work]
        - General, 1910s-80s, n.d. (Box 1024, Folder 1)
        - Clubs, 1905-21, n.d. (Box 1024, Folder 2)
        - Conferences, 1908-51 (Box 1024, Folder 3)
        - Business Office Culture Project, 1968-70
          - Dallas, Mt. Vernon, St. Louis, Tacoma (Box 1024, Folder 4)
          - Philadelphia, Pittsburgh (Box 1024, Folder 5)
        - Job Corps-YWCA Extension Residence Program, 1967-75, n.d.
          - Awards (Box 1024, Folder 6)
          - Buildings (Box 1024, Folder 7)
          - Classes, Personal Development (Box 1025, Folder 1)
          - Conferences (Box 1025, Folder 2)
          - Counseling, late 1960s (Box 1025, Folder 3)
          - Graduations (Box 1025, Folder 4)
          - Graduates, Groups (Box 1025, Folder 5-6)
          - Groups, snapshots (Box 1025, Folder 7)
          - Job skills training (Box 1025, Folder 8)
          - Staff, Leaders, and Speakers (Box 1025, Folder 9)
          - Recreation (Box 1025, Folder 10)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 1025, Folder 11)
        - Mill Villages work, 1900s-10s (Box 1025, Folder 12)
        - Non-Traditional Jobs for Women training programs, 1970s (Box 1025, Folder 13-14)
      - Immigration and Foreign Communities
        - General, 1910s-20s, 1960s-70s, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 1-2)
        - International Institutes, 1918, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 3)
      - Interracial/Racial Justice
        - American Indian Work, circa 1911, circa 1960-93, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 4)
        - "Colored Work"/Interracial: early photographs, 1910s-26 (Box 1026, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous activities and groups, 1960-98, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 6)
        - National Convocation on Racial Justice, 1972 (Box 1026, Folder 7)
        - Racial Justice Convocation, 1990 (Box 1026, Folder 8)
        - Racism: A Woman's Agenda, YWCA/Ladies Home Journal roundtable, 1993 (Box 1026, Folder 9)
        - Community Associations, 1970-76, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 10)
      - Teen Age and Younger Girls
        - General
          - General and miscellaneous, 1910s-90s, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 11-13)
          - National Teen Council (NTC)/National Teen Organization (NTO), 1972, 1993 (Box 1026, Folder 14)
          - Babysitter publicity series, circa 1960s (Box 1026, Folder 15)
          - Eight Week Clubs, 1910s (Box 1026, Folder 16)
          - International, n.d. (Box 1026, Folder 17)
        - Conferences, Consultations, and Assemblies
          - Younger Girls and Girl Reserve regional conferences, 1913-45 (Box 1027, Folder 1-3)
          - Y-Teens, regional and national Conferences
            - 1953-98, n.d. (Box 1027, Folder 4-7)
          - YMCA-YWCA National Conference for High School Youth, Grinnell College, Grinnell Iowa, 1947 (Box 1027, Folder 8-9)
          - First National Y-Teen Conference, Washington, DC, Nov 1956
            - General (Box 1027, Folder 10)
            - Numbered series (Box 1027, Folder 11-12)
            - Ceremonials (Box 1027, Folder 13)
          - Eastern Region Sectional Conference, Sarah Lawrence College, Bronxville, NY, 1962
            - General (Box 1027, Folder 14)
            - Campus and environs (Box 1027, Folder 15)
            - Discussion groups (Box 1028, Folder 1)
            - Migrant Camp visit (Box 1028, Folder 2-3)
            - Recreation and Religion (Box 1028, Folder 4)
          - Third National Y-Teen Conference, Washington, DC, 1965
            - General (Box 1028, Folder 5)
            - Embassy visits (Box 1028, Folder 6)
            - Folk Song Contest launch (Box 1028, Folder 7)
            - Speakers
              - Miscellaneous (Box 1028, Folder 8)
              - Hubert Humphrey (Box 1028, Folder 9)
          - National Teen Organization (NTO) Assembly, 1973, 1978, n.d. (Box 1028, Folder 10)
          - Consultation on the Job Market and Career Development, 1974 (Box 1028, Folder 11)
          - National Consultations on Teen Needs, 1981-82 (Box 1028, Folder 12)
          - National Teen Assembly (NTA), 1991 (Box 1028, Folder 13)
          - National Girls Conference, Jan 1997 (Box 1028, Folder 14)
        - Programs and Projects (National)
          - Neighborhood Youth Consumer Education Project, 1974 (Box 1028, Folder 15)
          - Summer Youth Demonstration Project, 1967
            - Group Discussions, Social Skills (Box 1028, Folder 16)
            - Office and Retail Skills (Box 1028, Folder 17)
            - Personnel (Box 1028, Folder 18)
            - Service Skills (Box 1028, Folder 19)
            - St. Louis (Box 1028, Folder 20)
          - TechGYRLS, 1997-98 (Box 1028, Folder 21)
          - Teen Counseling Project, 1971-73 (Box 1029)
            - General (Box 1029, Folder 1)
            - Event announcing publication of report "Attention is Needed... Action is Called For," 14 Jan 1974 (Box 1029, Folder 2)
          - Teen Pregnancy Prevention Program
            - Video "It's OK to say No Way": reception, 1985 (Box 1029, Folder 3)
            - Video "Lovesick": filming, n.d. (Box 1029, Folder 4)
          - United Nations Study Project, n.d. (Box 1029, Folder 5)
          - World Fellowship (Box 1029, Folder 6)
          - Young Women's Employment Training Project Educational Forums, 1986-87 (Box 1029, Folder 7)
          - Y-Teen Roll Call Week, 1948-65, n.d. (Box 1029, Folder 8)
          - National Y-Teen Week, 1979, 1982 (Box 1029, Folder 9-10)
        - Community Associations
          - General, 1956, 1963, n.d. (Box 1029, Folder 11)
          - Activities and programs, 1920-39, 1946-87, n.d. (Box 1029, Folder 12-13)
          - Classes, 1965-76 (Box 1030, Folder 1)
          - Groups, 1920-40, 1967-87, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 2-3)
          - Meetings, 1962, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 4)
          - Service Projects
            - Miscellaneous, 1953-76, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 5)
            - Anti-litter, 1968-69, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 6)
            - Children, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 7)
            - Hospitals, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 8)
      - Young Adults/Young Women Committed to Action
        - General, 1968, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 9)
        - Conferences, 1952-71 (Box 1030, Folder 10)
        - Y-Wives, circa 1940s-63 (Box 1030, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Services and Activities
      - General, 1964, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 12)
      - Bazaars and Thrift Shops, 1954-75, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 13)
      - Cafeterias, Coffee Shops and Lunch Rooms, 1910s-70s (Box 1030, Folder 14)
      - Child Care/Day Care, 1950s-80s, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 15-17)
      - Residences, 1910s-60s, n.d. (Box 1030, Folder 18)
    - Program Subjects
      - Camping and Outdoor Recreation
        - General, 1920s-80s (Box 1031, Folder 1-2)
        - Camps
          - Maqua, Poland, ME, 1910s-20s (Box 1031, Folder 3)
          - Community Associations
            - General, 1920s-90s (Box 1031, Folder 4)
            - Cavell, Detroit YWCA, 1910s-20s (Box 1031, Folder 5)
            - New Orleans, 1921, circa 1955 (Box 1031, Folder 6)
            - Quanicut, Pine Bush, NY, 1920s, n.d. (Box 1031, Folder 7)
            - Tennessee, circa 1950s (Box 1031, Folder 8)
        - Conservation
          - General, 1970s-80s (Box 1031, Folder 9)
          - Second National YWCA Conference on Outdoor Recreation and Conservation, 1966 (Box 1031, Folder 10)
          - Y-Teen Pilot Work Camp, Teton National Forest, 1966
            - General (Box 1031, Folder 11)
            - Dedication of Interpretive Trail (Box 1031, Folder 12)
            - Grand Tetons Scenes (Box 1031, Folder 13)
            - Film debut at White House, 1968 (Box 1031, Folder 14)
        - Playgrounds, 1910s-90s (Box 1031, Folder 15)
        - Vacation/Rest Homes, 1910s, n.d. (Box 1031, Folder 16)
      - Health
        - National program, general, 1910s-80s (Box 1031, Folder 17)
        - Community Associations, general, 1950s-90s (Box 1031, Folder 18)
        - International Conference of Women Physicians, 1919 (Box 1031, Folder 19)
        - Feet and Shoes, 1920s, 1960s (Box 1031, Folder 20)
        - ENCOREplus
          - National program, 1990s (Box 1031, Folder 21)
          - Breast Cancer Awareness postage stamp, 1996, n.d. (Box 1031, Folder 22)
          - Community Associations
            - General, 1970s-80s (Box 1032, Folder 1)
            - Miscellaneous Events, 1970s-90s (Box 1032, Folder 2-3)
        - Hospital and Invalid Care, 1910s-70s (Box 1032, Folder 4)
        - Pre-natal Care, 1950s-70s (Box 1032, Folder 5)
      - Sports and Fitness
        - Miscellaneous (Box 1032, Folder 6)
        - National Girls and Women in Sports Day (Box 1032, Folder 7)
        - Exercise Classes/Gymnastics
          - Adults, 1900s-90s, n.d. (Box 1032, Folder 8-10)
          - Children, 1960s-90s, n.d. (Box 1032, Folder 11-12)
          - Isometric exercises, 1960s (Box 1033, Folder 1)
          - Series of exercises for Nontraditional Jobs for Women Program, Brooklyn YWCA, circa 1980 (Box 1033, Folder 2)
        - Sports, Miscellaneous (Box 1033, Folder 3)
          - Basketball (Box 1033, Folder 4)
          - Bicycles (Box 1033, Folder 5)
          - Dance Classes and Dance Groups (Box 1033, Folder 6-7)
          - Fencing (Box 1033, Folder 8)
          - Golf (Box 1033, Folder 9)
          - Horseback Riding (Box 1033, Folder 10)
          - Racquet sports (Box 1033, Folder 11)
          - Self-defense/Martial Arts (Box 1033, Folder 12)
          - Skiing (Box 1033, Folder 13)
          - Swimming
            - General (Box 1033, Folder 14-15)
            - Children's classes (Box 1033, Folder 16)
            - Competitions/meets (Box 1033, Folder 17)
            - Skin Diving and Water Safety (Box 1034, Folder 1)
            - Handicapped (Box 1034, Folder 2)
          - Water Sports (Box 1034, Folder 3)
      - Recreation, [see also Camping and Outdoor Recreation]
        - General, 1970s (Box 1034, Folder 4)
        - Canteens 1940s-78 (Box 1034, Folder 5)
        - Classes
          - Miscellaneous, 1950s-70s (Box 1034, Folder 6)
          - Cooking, 1901-76, n.d. (Box 1034, Folder 7)
          - Crafts, 1950s-70s (Box 1034, Folder 8-9)
          - Group Work, 1970s? (Box 1034, Folder 10)
          - Languages, 1960s (Box 1034, Folder 11)
          - "Mr. and Mrs. Fixit," 1960s (Box 1034, Folder 12)
          - Painting and sculpture, 1901-70s (Box 1034, Folder 13)
          - Sewing, needlework, millinery, 1900s-20s (Box 1034, Folder 14)
          - Sewing, knitting, macramé, weaving, 1960s-80s (Box 1034, Folder 15)
          - Woodworking and home repair, 1960s-70s (Box 1034, Folder 16)
        - Dances, 1950s-80s (Box 1034, Folder 17)
        - Games, 1960s-70s (Box 1034, Folder 18)
        - Libraries/reading, 1960s (Box 1034, Folder 19)
        - Parties and events, 1900s-80s (Box 1035, Folder 1-2)
      - Music, 1963-92, n.d. (Box 1035, Folder 3)
      - Pageantry and Drama
        - General, 1910s-76, n.d. (Box 1035, Folder 4-5)
        - Water Carnivals and Pageants, 1930-56, n.d. (Box 1035, Folder 6)
      - Religion
        - General, 1915-16, late 1950s-75, n.d. (Box 1035, Folder 7)
        - Christmas, "Hanging of the Greens," 1936-70s, n.d. (Box 1035, Folder 8)
    - War Work and Defense Services
      - World War I
        - War Work staff (Box 1036, Folder 1)
        - Parades (Box 1036, Folder 2)
        - Patriotic League and homefront activities
          - General (Box 1036, Folder 3)
          - Automobile class, Lynchburg, Virginia (Box 1036, Folder 4)
          - Wireless classes (Box 1036, Folder 5)
        - Signal Corps (Box 1036, Folder 6)
        - Yeomenettes (Box 1036, Folder 7)
        - YWCA Hostess Houses
          - General (Box 1036, Folder 8)
          - California: Camp Kearney (Linda Vista) and Camp Freemont (Box 1036, Folder 9)
          - Florida
            - Camp Johnston (Box 1036, Folder 10)
            - Carlstrom Field, Dorr Field (Box 1036, Folder 11)
          - Georgia: Camp Gordon (Atlanta) (Box 1036, Folder 12)
          - Kansas: Camp Funston (Army City) (Box 1036, Folder 13)
          - Kentucky: Camp Zachary Taylor (Louisville) (Box 1036, Folder 14)
          - New Jersey: Camp Dix (Wrightstown) (Box 1036, Folder 15)
          - New York
            - Camp Yaphank (Upton, Long Island) (Box 1036, Folder 16)
            - New York City: 12 West 51st St, East 52nd St., and 375 Lexington Ave. (Box 1036, Folder 17)
            - Plattsburgh (Box 1036, Folder 18)
          - North Carolina: Camp Greene (Mecklenburg) and Oteen General Hospital (Box 1036, Folder 19)
          - Ohio: Camp Sherman (Chillicothe), Wilbur Wright Field (Dayton) (Box 1036, Folder 20)
          - Pennsylvania: Camp Crane (Allentown) (Box 1036, Folder 21)
          - Puerto Rico: Las Casas Camp (San Juan) (Box 1036, Folder 22)
          - Rhode Island: Naval Training Station (Newport) (Box 1036, Folder 23)
          - South Carolina: Camp Jackson (Columbia), Camp Sevier (Greenville), Camp Wadsworth (Spartanburg), Parris Island (Box 1036, Folder 24)
          - Tennessee: Fort Oglethorpe (Chattanooga) (Box 1036, Folder 25)
          - Texas
            - Camp Bowie (Fort Worth) (Box 1036, Folder 26)
            - Camp Logan (Houston) (Box 1036, Folder 27)
            - Ellington Field (Houston) (Box 1036, Folder 28)
            - Camp MacArthur (Waco) and Rich Field (Waco) (Box 1037, Folder 1)
            - Camp Stanley (Leon Springs) and Camp Travis (San Antonio) (Box 1037, Folder 2)
          - Virginia
            - Camp Lee (Petersburg) (Box 1037, Folder 3)
            - Marine Signal Corps (Quanitco) and Camp A.A. Humphreys (Box 1037, Folder 4)
          - Washington
            - Camp Lewis (American Lake) (Box 1037, Folder 5)
            - Navy Yard (Bremerton)-combination Hostess House and Club House (Box 1037, Folder 6)
            - Vancouver Barracks (Vancouver)-combination Hostess House and Club House (Box 1037, Folder 7)
        - YWCA housing and recreation for war workers
          - General (Box 1037, Folder 8)
          - Connecticut: industrial Girls' War Service Center and Camp (Box 1037, Folder 9)
          - New Jersey
            - Players' House, Camp Dix (Box 1037, Folder 10)
            - Industrial War Service Center, Bloomfield (Box 1037, Folder 11)
          - New York
            - Industrial Club House and Cafeteria, Bush Terminal, Brooklyn (Box 1037, Folder 12)
            - Recreation for nurses, New York City and Camp Mills (Box 1037, Folder 13)
            - Central Branch and West Side Branch, New York City (Box 1037, Folder 14)
            - War Service and Recreation Center for Colored Girls, 127 West 136th St., New York City (Box 1037, Folder 15)
          - Texas: Industrial Club Rooms and Centers (Box 1037, Folder 16)
          - Virginia: Industrial Center, Penniman (Box 1037, Folder 17)
          - Washington, DC: YWCA Country Club (Box 1037, Folder 18)
        - YWCA International work
          - General and miscellaneous (Box 1037, Folder 19)
          - Overseas staff (Box 1037, Folder 20)
          - France
            - General (Box 1037, Folder 21)
            - Recreation (Box 1037, Folder 22)
          - Poland
            - Polish Gray Samaritans (Box 1038, Folder 1)
            - Refugee work (Box 1038, Folder 2)
          - Training School for Old Country Service (Box 1038, Folder 3)
        - Women war workers [not YWCA photographs]
          - General and miscellaneous (Box 1038, Folder 4)
          - Construction (Box 1038, Folder 5)
          - Erie Railroad (Box 1038, Folder 6)
          - Mill work and factories (Box 1038, Folder 7)
          - Motion picture operator (Box 1038, Folder 8)
          - Packaging (Box 1038, Folder 9)
          - Michigan: munitions and steel, Detroit (Box 1038, Folder 10)
          - New Jersey
            - International Fuse and Arms Company, Bloomfield (Box 1038, Folder 11)
            - Shipyard, Newark (Box 1038, Folder 12)
          - New York
            - Brooklyn Rapid Transit (Box 1038, Folder 13)
            - Bush Terminal, Brooklyn (Box 1038, Folder 14)
            - Transportation, New York City (Box 1038, Folder 15)
          - Pennsylvania: Navy Yard, Philadelphia (Box 1038, Folder 16)
          - Virginia: Cotton Mills, Lynchburg (Box 1038, Folder 17)
          - France (Box 1038, Folder 18)
          - Great Britain (Box 1038, Folder 19)
        - Miscellaneous: Anna C. Ladd artificial faces for disfigured veterans (Box 1038, Folder 20)
      - World War II, [see also United Service Organizations below]
        - Japanese Evacuee Project, Relocation Center, Manzanaar, California, 1940s, 1943, 1989 (Box 1038, Folder 21)
        - International
          - General, n.d. (Box 1038, Folder 22)
          - YWCA War Service Centers, 1943-47 (Box 1038, Folder 23)
          - War relief work, circa 1944, 1945 (Box 1038, Folder 24)
          - Great Britain
            - General, 1939-44, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 1)
            - Hotel Victoria series, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 2)
            - The Palace Hut, Salisbury, 1944, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 3)
      - Defense Services
        - United Community Defense Services
          - General, 1954, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 4)
          - San Diego, California, 1952-53, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 5)
          - Savannah River site, Georgia and South Carolina, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 6)
          - Portsmouth Gaseous Diffusion Plant, Piketon, Ohio, 1952, circa 1955 (Box 1039, Folder 7-8)
        - United Service Organizations (USO)
          - General, 1941-45; 1953-73, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 9-10)
          - YWCA USO Division, 1946-70, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 11)
          - Anniversary (25th), 1966 (Box 1039, Folder 12)
          - Clubs
            - General, 1946-67 (Box 1039, Folder 13)
            - Anniversaries, 1944-62 (Box 1039, Folder 14)
            - Openings, 1952-67, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 15-16)
          - Staff, 1944-69, n.d. (Box 1039, Folder 17-18)
          - Staff Conferences, 1952-69 (Box 1039, Folder 19)
  - Subseries F. Student Work
    - General and Miscellaneous
      - Prints, 1910s-80s, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 1-2)
      - Negatives, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 3)
    - Alumnae Network, 1984 (Box 1040, Folder 4)
    - Conferences, Regional
      - Asilomar/Pacific Coast, 1900, 1920 (Box 1040, Folder 5)
      - Geneva/Mid-West/Central, 1872-1950s, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 6-11)
      - Middle Atlantic/Eagles Mere/East Central, 1911-18 (Box 1040, Folder 12)
      - New England/Maqua, 1920-21 (Box 1040, Folder 13)
      - Pacific Northwest/Seabeck, 1913-57 (Box 1040, Folder 14)
      - Rocky Mountain/Western/Estes, 1906-07, 1920, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 15)
      - Silver Bay/Eastern/Northeast, 1914-17 (Box 1040, Folder 16)
      - Southern, 1898-53, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 17-18)
      - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 1930s, 1969, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 19)
    - Councils
      - National Student Council of the YWCA
        - General, 1949-92, n.d. (Box 1040, Folder 20)
        - Issue Network on Higher Education, circa 1969-70 (Box 1041, Folder 1)
        - Leaders, group photos, 1950s-80s (Box 1041, Folder 2)
      - Regional Councils, 1931, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 3)
    - National Student Assembly of the YWCA (NSC), 1970-92, n.d., [see also Organizations, YMCA and YWCA below] (Box 1041, Folder 4)
    - Organizations
      - International, 1911-31, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 5)
      - YMCA and YWCA (Box 1041)
        - National Intercollegiate Christian Council (NICC), 1942-50 (Box 1041, Folder 6)
        - National Student Council of the YMCA and YWCA (NSCY)
          - General, 1953-61, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 7)
          - Officers, 1951-62, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 8)
        - National Student Assembly of the YMCA and YWCA, 1963, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 9)
    - Programs and Projects
      - Miscellaneous, 1929, 1966-68, n.d. (Box 1041, Folder 10)
      - Asian Seminar, 1960s (Box 1041, Folder 11)